

Ria Ghosh Dastidar

Responsible professional, passionate about delivering outstanding quality and service. Offering 6 years of experience in industry with history of recognition for performance. Diligently follows procedures and handle issues in full. Balances customer desires with organizational standards to create mutually beneficial solutions to diverse problems. Consistently exceeds performance and service quality targets.

ghoshdastidarria52@gmail.com



8420362385



Kolkata, India



27 April, 1994

WORK EXPERIENCE

Advertiser Support Associate

Amazon Development Centre India Pvt. Ltd.

07/2020 - 09/2023

Responsibilities

- Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems
- Resolving issues and complexities for advertiser via email and live channels
- Handling escalation, dive-deep on cases and support leads, associates
- Engaged with customers to better understand needs and deliver excellent service
- Work on initiatives/projects to improve quality and efficiency of the process
- Collaborated with team members to achieve target results

Venue Manager

Oravel Stays Pvt. Ltd.

07/2019 - 05/2020

Responsibilities

- Get in touch with the customers and provide them with quotation
- Co-ordinate with the 3rd party vendors to ensure all the commitments are delivered
- Work with the corporate team to market the venue and execute any local marketing initiatives
- Ensure a healthy relation with the venue owner and other stakeholders
- o Communicated booking, payment and cancellation confirmations to customers and updated internal records to match

Business Development Manager

Inyt Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

08/2018 - 07/2019

Responsibilities

- Developing and generating new business through cold calling, referrals, leads follow up and customize the sales strategies
- Maintaining relationships with existing franchisees and engaging with them to evolve business models
- · Liaise with the Marketing and Business Support team on the planning of setting up the Franchisee operations
- Co-ordinate, setup and manage new outlets opening from ground zero to smooth opening

Senior Education Counsellor

Esteem Infocon Pvt Ltd

02/2017 - 08/2018

Responsibilities

- To generate leads via cold callings, referrals
- Counseled students working through educational problems
- To ensure good relation with the colleges and other stakeholders
- To organize events and seminars
- To manage day to day operations of the company

SKILLS

Process Knowledge Quality focused Customer satisfaction Active listening Communication skills **Customer Relations** Team player **Problem Solving** Administrative support Coordinating events Well-organized Hospitality Positive attitude

EDUCATION

MBA

Jadavpur University

06/2015 - 07/2018

Bachelor of Commerce

Calcutta University

06/2012 - 07/2015

National Gems Higher Secondary School

2012

— ICSE

National Gems Higher Secondary School

2010